That's the rabbit?
Timothy?
Come out, Timothy!
I'm right here.
Timothy!
So weird...
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
meditation    homecoming
It is senseless to involve oneself with an escapee.
However, I believe it is only natural
that deviants of Romdeau be punished.
A generalization.
Preaching generalizations is for
those who do not practice business.
Be mindful of the fact that you
are the Citizen Security Bureau Chief.
Understood.
Blood pressure and pulse rate are both increasing.
Respiratory rate changing.
Are you analyzing me?
What is the point in analyzing a
human who is under emotional control?
That arrogance invites error.
Are you all right,
Sir?
What a vile face.
It is something...
that taints me.
Daedalus!
I'm cold...
The high fever will cause your skin and blood vessels to contract,
resulting in chills and spasms,
eventually leading to death.
Where's Vincent?!
Where is he?!
Is he already-
No.
He hasn't left yet.
But tomorrow he'll probably...
Dammit.
In your condition, you shouldn't overexert yourself.
Vincent Law...
the only clue that could help me solve the mystery of PROXY.
Dammit.
Dang, it won't even make a single sound.
It's the newest model from Romdeau all right.
It's snobby.
Oh, we were just looking for you.
You're good with machines, aren't you?
How do you-
Why do you have this?
Did you steal it?
"Steal"?
It wasn't Hoody's in the first place.
Quinn said
that she's going to use this to lure that negotiator here.
What?
That woman's gone a bit crazy ever since Timothy died.
Well, we have too.
What?
Where is Vincent Law?
Who knows.
You're the one who stole my AHT, aren't you?
Would you like me to give it back?
I'm going to take that man back with me to Romdeau.
I won't let him go with you.
Take him back on that?
Choose the man or the vehicle.
You're pathetic, Princess.
Miss Re-l!
Vin... cent!
Hoody doesn't have the vaccine.
It ran out
a long time ago.
He's hidden that fact from the folks here, though.
But my illness. He...
Treated it, he said?
That's a lie.
You recovered on your own.
There's no... medicine?
But...
That's...
The last one.
But I can't just give it to you for free.
If you'll bring that girl
to the rabbit, I'll give this to you.
Don't frown.
She'll recover as long as she gets this.
The more the merrier, you know...
when you travel.
Hoody.
Ah, Pino.
What are you doing?
Nothing...
nothing at all.
You're leaving this place tomorrow, aren't you.
That's right.
You don't want to go back to Romdeau?
Not really.
Why not?
Well, I can't leave Vince alone.
Oh, but Pa-
No, it's nothing.
Hey, Hoody.
Do you know where Timothy is?
I've been looking for him, but I can't find him anywhere.
Timothy died, didn't he?
Yeah, that's right.
So, I was wondering if there was another Timothy.
Pino...
When people die, you can never see them ever again.
What?
Really?
Really.
Really...
I wish I could've played with him more.
Are you lonely, Pino?
"Lonely"?
Yes.
Right now, the feeling you have right there
is loneliness.
"Loneliness"...
Damn.
And we managed to lure the girl over, too.
Be patient.
We still have the girl's vehicle.
Besides, we're better off not angering that man.
What? That's not like you.
You 'fraid of that sprout?
Who knows? I wonder myself.
I brought them, Quinn.
Wow.
What are these?
So many...
I have sown the seed.
Now we'll see how he responds.
I'll take you with me.
I have no other choice!
Vince?
You intend to take the girl?
Even if she stays here, she won't be cured of the infection.
Vincent, what are you say-
You know that better than anyone!
You knew?
If we get on that ship, we can get the vaccine.
You're saying that Quinn will save that girl?
Fool!
She's of Romdeau - they took Timothy's life.
Once you take off on the rabbit, the dome will pursue you for sure.
If you use that girl as a shield, they won't be able to attack.
But once you make it through the bay
and shake off your pursuers, she'll have outlived her usefulness.
Quinn's promise to help her is a lie.
You'd be a fool to believe her.
But if there's a vaccine-
That vaccine was fake.
Even if it were real, in the extreme cold outside...
In her weakened state...
Even so, if things go on like this...
Yes.
She won't last much longer.
Then what are you saying I should do?!
Return her to Romdeau.
Return her... to Romdeau?
If you don't want her to die,
you have no choice but to return her to Romdeau.
I don't know what you did in the dome,
but that girl came to take you back.
You're someone special - someone who can go back.
Those of Romdeau go back to Romdeau.
It's the way of things.
If you rebel against it, you will rot away.
Return... to Romdeau.
Quinn.
Come here.
Quinn!
He's thinking of going back to Romdeau?
Take this.
Take care of yourself.
You too.
You're going back to Romdeau, Miss Re-l.
Hop, hop, hop...
Hop, hop!
Plane!
We're leaving!
Pino...
Bye bye...
Re-l Mayer, you said?
An AHT is currently docked outside of Plugvent 3.
Regarding its reentry, the Administrative Bureau is-
Now of all times...
Chief.
Let it wait.
It's only natural to disallow the return of
those who leave the dome without permission
and punish those who leave and become deviants.
It's a generalization indeed.
No,
it is why one must be absolute.
Isn't that right, Kristeva?
There are no waves.
Well?
Nothing. I'm clueless about machines.
It'd better not sink.
If I were to commit suicide with someone, I'd pick a better man.
True 'nuff.
Stupid.
She's talking about you.
Whaaat?
In any case,
reconnect the severed lines.
It can just be a temporary fix.
But Quinn...
It's quiet.
Is it because there's no wind?
No...
Not just because there's no wind.
Quinn, are a lot of scary things coming?
Don't worry.
You're like Papa, Quinn.
Hey, you mean "Mama", don't you?
I don't really understand.
Dammit.
Not here.
Hurry up!
Or you'll be full of holes!
Anything from Chief Raul?
Not yet.
Useless.
As we suspected, Re-l Mayer's infection is-
That's a headache.
Her passenger, who has identified himself as Vincent Law,
was previously wanted by the Security Bureau.
Shall we report him?
She brought him back.
He's worth a look.
Just report that there was a passenger.
We can say we didn't know he was Vincent.
Sir?
You think it's a bad idea?
However, I am not so kind as to show cards
I am not required to disclose.
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Report, Hokim!
Damn! Damn!
Stay down, Pino!
Chief Raul.
It was just getting good, too.
I am sure you have received our
request for the release of Plugvent 3.
The outside air is full of pathogens.
Considering the additional fact that she is infected,
I cannot approve the release that easily.
I believe we've given you enough time to consider,
Security Bureau Chief.
We've taken all the necessary precautions.
Please approve the release.
I have no choice.
We shall deal with her passenger as well.
Passenger?
It's not just that upstart girl?
Vincent Law...
Leave three of the pursuit units
and have the rest go to Plugvent 3.
I will go there as well.
Yes, sir.
He's there.
He's not on the wing ship.
What's going on?
There.
In any case, this is our chance.
Get it fixed!
That's strange...
I haven't heard the name of this passenger.
Why do you think it's him?
That's just a guess, no?
However, the possibility of it being true is high.
Vincent Law...
Charged with treason for destroying an Entourage.
He's just an immigrant.
He may be dissentious,
but he doesn't seem to warrant a
full-fledged pursuit by the Security Bureau.
As I said, it just goes to show we shouldn't be bothered
by such an unremarkable man more than we have to be.
Excuse me.
It's just that you seem rather obsessed.
Re-l Mayer is on the other side of the hatch, Chairman Daedalus.
It would be best that you not forget that fact.
All right, I understand.
The passenger, Vincent Law,
will be executed immediately upon identity confirmation.
Can't be helped.
Re-l is our highest priority right now.
Tell them that they will regret it if they harm Re-l in any way.
Releasing plugvent.
Do we have your permission, sir?
Yes.
Go ahead.
Releasing hatch.
Show your face, Vincent.
We did it!
It moved!
It's moving!
Good job, kid.
This is how it should be.
Quinn!
The wing ship has left the bay.
The surveillance units will not be able to engage in further pursuit.
Burn the Commune to the ground!
Miss Quinn...
This...
Liquor.
The really good kind.
Be thankful...
when you drink it.
We can still go back to the Commune.
Let's go back and treat your injuries!
Quinn!
Quinn...
Jeez,
listen to yourselves.
Look.
They're acting lost because they can't come over here.
To think that we were all so scared of those stupid things...
What a joke.
Serves them right.
Every last one of them...
Quinn!
Quinn...
Quinn...?
I'm...
lonely, Quinn.
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
The days of ignorant bliss have ended.
The unseen force that bars my path has been revealed.
meditation  re-l 124C41+
And...